[upbeat music plays]
[engine turns over]
[engine revs, horn honks]
[Jerry] This is a 1966
Porsche 356SC Cabriolet
in light ivory.
It weighs 1,980 pounds.
It has a powerful
1.6 liter flat-four engine.
This car was at one time
a Dutch police car.
In 1966, Porsche had finished building
the 356 and began producing the 911.
But the Dutch Police Department
like convertibles for their visibility,
to catch those Dutch crooks
that are always up to something.
Who made the hole in the dike
to begin with?
And who cut this kid's hair like that?
I'd like to ask them a few questions.
Let's round 'em up.
[siren wails]
So they asked Porsche,
"Can you just make us ten more
of the car that you used to make
and don't make any more?"
Imagine asking a car company today,
"Hey, remember that car you made
a couple years ago?
We need ten more of 'em."
And Porsche went, "Okay, ten more."
So, they retooled
their entire production line
just to make ten more of these
for the Dutch Police Department.
Here they are.
And of the ten they made,
this is the tenth of the ten.
So, it is the very last Porsche 356
ever made.
That's why they put the flowers
on the hood.
Here it is in '66.
Here I am driving it today.
[engine turns over]
So, it was the last 356,
but it is also the first car I ever used
for the very first episode
of Comedians in Cars Getting Coffee
with my friend, comedian, writer,
and creator of the Ted L. Nancy
book series, Barry Marder.
So, I had this idea.
But I didn't have the confidence in it
that you had.
And Barry encouraged me
to make the first show,
which we did back in 2012.
-[Barry makes trumpeting sound]
-[Jerry laughs]
-[Jerry] So, here we are six years later.
-This is what started it.
And I wanted to bring Barry back,
since he was the one
who is really responsible
for me getting this thing going.
Let's toast to what we accomplished.
Barry is one of my closest friends.
We talk everyday.
We always have fun,
and I am looking forward to doing
that same thing again with him today.
[phone rings]
[Barry] Hello?
Hello?
-[Jerry] Hello?
-[Barry] Hello?
-[Jerry] Who is this?
-[Barry] Who is this?
[Jerry] What's up, dog?
People think because something happened
in their day where something went awry,
that it's an interesting story.
Guess what happened to me?
I went to the dentist.
I had a two o'clock appointment.
Turns out, he couldn't take me till 2:30.
So I sat there for a half an hour.
-[Barry] Yeah.
-[Jerry] It's a bad story.
-[Barry] It's not a good story.
-[Jerry] Shut up.
Well, I do have an exciting car for you.
I'm really looking forward to seeing you.
-Have you had coffee yet?
-[Barry] Nope.
-Great. Be there in a couple minutes.
-[Barry] All right.
[Jerry] And that is why
I am Jerry Seinfeld,
and this is
Comedians in Cars Getting Coffee.
[Barry] I love this car.
[engine turns over]
[upbeat music plays]
-[Jerry] What was your first car?
-A used Corvair.
My dad had bought me that car.
The death car.
We were pulling up next to a, uh...
a bookstore.
The whole bookstore was lined
with Unsafe at Any Speed by Ralph Nader.
I said, "Isn't that the car
you bought me?"
Couldn't wait till I turned 16
to buy me a death trap.
You got to admit,
this is a very pleasant experience.
[jazz plays]
I was looking at this magazine cover.
It said, "Caitlyn Jenner Without Makeup."
Isn't that Bruce Jenner?
It is.
[Barry] Where are we headed to?
-Or you're gonna surprise me?
-It's a surprise.
The owner of the parking facility
in front of the deli,
who received his law degree in 1951,
has sent a cease-and-desist letter.
He's threatening legal action.
If we go into the parking lot
and do not shop...
But if you're eating in the deli,
isn't that shopping?
I think the key number here is
-"law degree in '51."
-[Barry laughs]
That is a 7-Eleven
that has been turned into a school.
That looks like the school
that you went to
where you got
your high school equivalency.
I went to, literally, a motel,
'cause I needed this thing
to get into the Air Force.
-Right.
-I told him,
"I... I've never seen the diploma."
And he... he ran it in front of me
really quick.
It was an incidental bill, I think.
My diploma had a club sandwich on it
and some phone charges.
[jazz plays]
I like the fire map on the back door
of the, uh, hotel room.
-Yes.
-And it always says, "Don't panic."
-And even if you did panic...
-Yeah.
...you have a perfect excuse.
Gee, I heard they found you naked,
swinging from the shower curtain
with the ice bucket on your head.
-What happened?
-Yeah.
-I panicked.
This is you and I all day, every day.
-All day, every day.
So, I asked my kids to rate
eating, drinking, peeing, and pooping,
one to four.
Eating, drinking, peeing, and pooping.
If you gotta poop, you gotta poop.
So, you're putting that at number one?
-I would say number one.
-I... Oh, that's ridiculous.
Because there's so many more
enjoyable aspects to eating.
You get to think about it, talk about it,
choose where you're gonna eat.
Then, you get to order the food,
you get to anticipate it.
You have... you could have an appetizer.
-You could have a salad.
-You get many second dates?
-[Jerry laughs]
-Huh?
-[Jerry] What a beautiful day.
-[Barry] It is nice out here.
[jazz plays]
I really just want the waitress
to bring me some coffee.
-I have not had any coffee.
-I haven't had any either.
We should get some coffee.
This is what I like about this restaurant.
-Yeah.
-They advertise,
"Guaranteed view of a heavy person
from anywhere in the restaurant."
[Jerry laughing]
The whole place looks like
the Disney Jamboree Bears. Really.
Do you remember when the Disney
Jamboree Bear was an absurd concept?
-The Jamboree Bears at Disney...
-Yeah.
-It was crazy. "Let's take bears...
-Right.
...and put them in human clothes."
Vests, hats,
collar with a bow tie.
Now, it's normal.
And now it's a guy
walking down the street.
[jazz plays]
This is why I love my girlfriend,
even though we're both heavy.
Let's say she's on top of me
and were intimate.
And I'm uncomfortable.
She lets me tap out.
I can go like this
and she'll roll right off.
We are under MMA rules now
during our... our intimacy.
Wow, that coffee is good and strong.
It's hitting me. I love it.
[jazz plays]
This Jeff Sessions looks like
the last surviving Munchkin
from Lollipop Land, doesn't he?
No. He's Elven.
-He's an Elven guy, isn't he?
-Yeah, he's Elven.
You can't get the elf out of a man.
[Jerry laughs]
[jazz plays]
If I could find
some camouflage pants to fit me,
I would shoot this town up.
I love the little, uh... [clears throat]
People always doing these things.
Yeah. After they eat,
there's always a lot of...
[Barry] Yeah.
Now, I won't eat again till I get home.
[Jerry laughs]
-'Cause you're on that fasting program.
-Yep.
-You don't eat anything in between eating.
-Nothing.
[jazz plays]
[woman] How you doing here?
-Fantastic.
-Great.
-Would you like some more?
-Um, I'll wait. Thank you.
Who tells someone, "You want dessert?"
while they're eating?
"Would you like an eclair?" What?
People just drive me crazy.
I was at an event the other day.
I was having a conversation with somebody,
one of the event people
comes over and says,
"We're not doing anything yet,
but I'll let you know."
Then don't say anything.
-Yeah.
-You see I'm having a conversation.
Can't you see people talking?
-Can't you see that?
-No.
[jazz plays]
I just like to talk.
When I say something crazy
and go, "Here's what the psychiatrist
just wrote on his pad."
And he's doodling on his pad
'cause he's got...
he's got seven circles in a row...
-Yeah.
-...and the pyramid with the eye on it.
-Right. Right.
-He's got his own problems.
You're just the 45-minute, $690 fee.
He goes, "Says he just likes to talk."
[Jerry laughs]
You know?
-While he looks at his watch.
-"Increase promazine."
Yeah.
[jazz plays]
Why do men wear toupees?
-If you are in a bar...
-Yeah.
...and you are talking
to a very attractive young lady...
But at some point in the relationship
you have to reveal to the person...
"By the way..."
She may have to reveal something to you.
When I was married to Laura,
my fourth wife,
I pulled out a clump of her hair.
-And I thought, "What is this?"
-Yes.
-A clump of hair came out in your hand?
-Right.
It would have had to been
an intimate moment since I never,
you know, would ever harm her.
She had a weave,
-kind of weave in there.
-[Jerry] Oh.
-[Barry] A big clump.
-Oh, my.
I immediately took a knee
and blew the whistle.
-And I threw a yellow flag onto the play.
-[Jerry] Yeah.
[upbeat music plays]
We passed Lowe's. [laughs]
[coughs]
You sound great.
[both laugh]
You know, there is such a thing
as overtraining.
-You don't mind if I have a Ricola?
-No, that's nice.
I like people that bring
their own Uber snacks...
-[Barry laughs]
-...in their back pocket.
So you're losing weight,
-you got a fantastic girlfriend.
-I told her--
-You got a pocket full of snacks.
-Yeah.
You're all set.
[jazz plays]
-There it is, Big Lots.
-I knew there was one around here.
I've always wanted to go to a Big Lots.
You know what I like about Big Lots?
-[Barry] What?
-The exclamation point.
-That's what you like about 'em?
-I like the enthusiasm.
I like that they're excited about it.
-Yeah.
-I've never been in one of these stores.
I have. You like big?
-Yeah.
-You like lots?
-You got it.
-[man] Hi.
-[Jerry] How are you?
[Jerry] I could wander around
a store like this for hours.
[Barry] Why?
I just like things in packages
and with words on them.
That's everything.
[Jerry laughs]
-Really.
-No, it's not.
-Yosemite is not like that.
-This could be used as a weapon.
[Jerry laughs]
You could literally fend off someone
with a Classic Cookie Collection.
Really.
You start jabbing at somebody with that,
you got a weapon, my friend. Yeah.
"Back off,
I got a Classic Cookie Collection."
[jazz plays]
Let me get this straight, you like things
that have writing on them.
Yes. I like boxes and containers
with writing on it.
'Cause the writing
tells you what's in there.
Nobody's more observant than you.
Oh, look at these cereals. Wow!
-This is really where you shine.
-[Jerry] Oh, baby. Bring it on.
Let me tell you what it's all about
right now.
What's your favorite cereal, all-time?
I would probably have to say
Kellogg's Bran Flakes.
-Bran flakes?
-I like them.
No wonder you had a depressed childhood.
[Jerry] I like the acknowledgment...
that you're gonna need it.
Why are you just getting one?
Why don't I just get a lot?
Why you're not in timeshare business,
I don't know.
-This is fun, isn't it?
-Yeah.
[jazz plays]
You were working at The Comedy Store,
and you were getting by
selling jokes to other comedians.
I was selling jokes to Jay Leno,
and Letterman,
and Garry Shandling, and Bill Maher,
and I was getting $75 a joke back then.
Seventy-five dollars a joke?
So, my father says to me,
"How you making money?"
And I explained that to him.
He would say, "Why would they pay you
that much money for a joke?"
And I'd go, "Because the people
that need the jokes
-really need them."
-[Jerry laughs]
The guys that need 'em...
-really need 'em.
-Really need them.
-[Barry] I'm here. I'm having fun.
-Me too. I'm having fun.
This is boarding,
particle boarding for a room.
-This is a shelf.
-Yeah. [laughs]
-This is a--
-You could finish a deck with this.
How much bigger candy do you want,
for God's sake? This is a sampler?
-That's not even a whole box?
-No, it's just a sample.
Yeah.
If you like it,
we'll give you the big one.
[laughs] Yeah.
By the way,
do you recall, it wasn't too long ago
that Twinkie went out of business,
and then somebody swooped in
and bought the name?
-I think so.
-Remember that?
-Yep.
-So, it's exciting that they're back.
-You wanna get a Twinkie?
-Yes!
[Jerry] Look at this, a chocolate Twinkie.
-I never even heard of this.
-You haven't?
-I never heard of this.
-Come to my house later.
That looks good, fudge covered.
-Think we could lose weight eating this?
-Yeah.
[woman] Do you have
a rewards card with us?
[Barry] A rewards card?
This is the reward right here.
This is gonna be fun.
This is my idea of a fun day.
[jazz plays]
[Jerry eating] This is really good.
Drake's came out with a Yodel,
and it came in a box, and each Drake...
Am I boring you?
[both laugh]
[upbeat music plays]
-[woman] Jerry, I love the show!
-[Jerry] Thank you!
[Jerry] You too, sweetie.
Is that, um...
-inappropriate?
-What?
-I called her "sweetie." Is that...
-That's a write-up.
[laughs]
Highlight of my day so far
is the Twinkies.
No offense.
[upbeat music plays]
-[woman] Hi, welcome to BevMo!
-Thank you.
I love it.
I hope I can find something to drink.
[jazz plays]
[Jerry whispering] It's a lot of booze.
It's all booze.
I thought it was
all different kinds of beverages.
-It's just booze.
-Booze.
Does everybody that comes in this store
have a problem?
Everyone that goes into any store
has a problem, Jerry.
Very few people are free of any problems.
-I really like cute, little things.
-Why don't you buy that?
I don't like the flavor of this stuff.
I'd rather get some more Twinkie products.
[upbeat jazz plays]
Now, tomorrow,
I'm going to get my ear fixed.
-What's that?
-I'm getting my ear fix--
-That was a joke.
-Oh.
I hope the guy can do it.
Well, out of the two people in the room,
he would have the best shot.
My brother and I hang out.
We sit and we watch TV. We have fun.
Well, he lives in your house.
What choice do you have?
-Al Jaffee's snappy answers...
-[Jerry laughs]
...to roommate situations.
"We pass each other in the hall."
"Well, he lives there."
"I see him around a lot."
"Yeah, you're roommates."
-"He was in the garage, getting his car."
-Yeah.
[Jerry laughs]
Such a nice ride in this car today.
Enjoyable being outside in the sun,
in an open car that runs nice,
just like it was six years ago.
I don't know what I'd do without you.
-What are you gonna do now?
-Um, nothing.
-Thank you again.
-Okay.
-Appreciate it. Thanks.
-Thank you.
[sentimental instrumental music plays]
[door lock opens]
Jerry, it's... it's over.
-All right.
-Thank you.
Really.
All right, all right, I'm going.
Aye. [sighs]